<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Hyde</title>
    <link>https://hyde.thedataareclean.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Hyde</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hyde.thedataareclean.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Life as a Productivity Tool..</title>
      <link>https://hyde.thedataareclean.com/post/2021-04-21-life-productivity-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hyde.thedataareclean.com/post/2021-04-21-life-productivity-tool/</guid>
      <description>A new tool is spotted in the wild ! I love productivity tools. Correction, I am obsessed with productivity tools. To-Dos, Notes, Planners, all kinds. If there is a tool that was released, I have probably tried it, trying it right now and saving up time and money to do it soon. It’s a problem, I am working on it.
 The Cycle of (percieved) Improvement The cycle of testing this tools also always follow the same pattern:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How much of you is you ?</title>
      <link>https://hyde.thedataareclean.com/post/2021-01-10-how-much-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hyde.thedataareclean.com/post/2021-01-10-how-much-you/</guid>
      <description>Are there days you just don’t identify with yourself? This person that you have become. The likes and dislikes you tell yourself and the world, your interests and your habits. Every last detail about you. None of it feels like you, it feels like a version of you that you adopted because it was the most convenient one. Or worse, capitalism convinced you that you are this person even though you end some days feeling disconnected with every part of or you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Beginnings !</title>
      <link>https://hyde.thedataareclean.com/post/2021-01-02-new-beginnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hyde.thedataareclean.com/post/2021-01-02-new-beginnings/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone, welcome to my new microblog. A fancy way of saying this is a place where I write down my feelings that are may be a tad bit too touchy to hamper my employment opportunities. Then again, if a prospect employer is hurt by any of the content here, maybe I shouldn’t be working with them. &amp;lt;&amp;lt; makes mental note &amp;gt;&amp;gt;
But coming back to the topic at hand, welcome to the microblog!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>